YYeTs.com
人人影視
*Better pray for hell*
時間軸： 濃子   芝麻圓子    校對： 蘇小黛   胖兔純
Good morning.
早上好
I, uh, am here to collect a parcel incoming on that vessel.
剛來的那艘船上有我的一個包裹
Influenza outbreak.
流感爆發了
Five dead.
死了五個人
Frigate's under quarantine.
那艘船被隔離了
Quarantine?
隔離
By whose order?
誰下的令
George Sibley.
喬治·西布里
By way of his wife, Mary Sibley.
是他妻子瑪麗·西布里代為下令的
Does a man desire
你們男人會渴望
to know when he is on the precipice of his own death?
知道自己什么時候會歸天嗎
What say you, George?
喬治  你說...
Would your friend, the blacksmith,
你那個鐵匠朋友
want to know that scant hours from now,
會想知道還有多久
Mercy Lewis will accuse him of witchcraft?
梅西·路易絲就會控告他巫師罪嗎
From which his trial and execution will swiftly follow?
然后他的審判和處決就將接踵而來
Or would he favor
還是他更想
his waning moments be spent in ignorance?
毫不知情地度過這所剩無多的時間
Oh, don't pity him, George.
別為他難過  喬治
It is the blood of innocents like your friend
正是你這些無辜朋友的血
that make our grand rite possible.
才讓我們的大祭典成為可能
Each accusation made,
每一次控告和審判
each trial convened not for us, but by us.
都不是針對我們  而是由我們掌控的
No one the wiser to our plan
沒人會想到我們的計劃
and nobody brave enough to stand in our way.
也沒人膽敢阻止我們的腳步
You miss them, don't you?
你想念他們  對吧
When I was young,
我小時候
I thought them horribly sensible people.
一直認為他們都是壞人
Now...
但現在...
Salem could use more like them.
塞勒姆缺的正是他們
I'm intruding, captain.
抱歉打擾了  上尉
No, no.
不  不
I'm glad you're amongst the living...
很高興你還活著
So to speak.
恕我直言
Word was you had taken quite ill.
我聽說你病的不輕
Indeed.
確實如此
A fit that came on suddenly and without reason,
不知為何  我突然就發作了
followed by a restless sleep
睡也睡不安穩
in which the sickness infected even my dreams.
那疾病似乎感染了我的夢境
Your dreams?
你的夢境
I dreamt of a doll with eyes full and black.
我夢到一只沒有眼白的玩偶
And when I awoke, feverish in the night's middle,
我半夜醒來  渾身高熱
I could have sworn the doll was there, staring back at me.
我發誓那只玩偶也在那盯著我
Fever dreams can be quite vivid.
高熱會使你產生幻覺
Except I could have sworn
但我發誓
that I saw my father enter in darkness
我看到我父親走入了黑暗之中
and remove the doll.
拿走了那只玩偶
But when I asked, he laughed and assured me that...
但只要我一提起  他就笑著跟我說...
You were dreaming.
你是在做夢
Do you doubt my father's veracity, Captain Alden?
你也覺得不可信對嗎  奧登上尉
No.
不
But it seems like you do.
但這似乎你是這么想的
I...
我...
I have no doubt that he's a good man.
毫無疑問他是個好人
But lately...
但最近...
What?
什么
Had I but known you were in such safe hands,
早知道你跟他在一起
I would have spared your mother her worry.
你母親就不用那么擔心了
Magistrate.
治安官
Come along, Anne.
走吧  安
Let us allow captain Alden his privacy.
不要打擾奧登上尉了
Have I heard you correctly?
我沒聽錯吧
Are you suggesting that Anne Hale is the victim of...
你是說安·霍爾是受害者  她被...
A spell.
下咒了
Am I, too, the victim of a spell?
我也被下咒了嗎
Or has John Alden finally declared his belief in witches?
還是約翰·奧登終于相信有巫師存在了
I've seen too much to deny any longer,
我親眼所見太多證據  無法否認了
making my next step obvious...catching one.
所以很明顯我下一步...要抓一個巫師
As you know, apprehending a witch is no easy feat.
你也知道  抓捕巫師不是件容易的事
Unless you know who they are.
只要知道他們是誰就不難
Have you uncovered the conjurer who spelled Anne?
你找到給安下咒的巫師了嗎
Who is it?
是誰
Tell me.
告訴我
Someone in proximity to his victim.
一個與受害者很親近的人
Yes.
對
Whose own daughter voices her suspicions.
他自己的女兒也說出了自己的懷疑
Magistrate Hale?
霍爾治安官嗎
He's not who he seems.
他不是大家所想的那樣
Who amongst us is?
我們之中誰是
You?
你嗎
Or I?
還是我
Who among us is unburdened by shame
我們當中誰沒有
or secrets that we hide from the world?
不為人知的恥辱或者秘密
I'm Reverend Mather.
我是麥哲牧師
Is there a problem?
你有問題嗎
Well, no.
沒有
The lady and I were just discussing some business.
這位女士剛跟我談生意呢
- Business? - Yes.
-生意  -對
As in how much it might cost me to get down to some...
比如我要花多少錢才能...
This is a reputable establishment!
這里是個受人尊敬的地方
It offers no place for your lechery.
不許你在這里縱欲淫蕩
- Reverend. - Reverend.
-牧師  -牧師
Cotton!
柯頓
Pardon me.
不好意思
I apologize if I've caused any offense.
如有冒犯  我在此道歉
Good day.
日安
Do you know that man?
你認識那人嗎
Never seen him before.
從未見過
Ring around the rosies
玫瑰花環
Pocketful of posies
花束千萬
Ashes, ashes
灰燼飄落
We all fall down
人死歸天
Ah, Yeah.
不錯
She has arrived.
她來了
Mercy.
梅西
My dear, this is a blessing.
親愛的  真是上帝保佑
Truly.
確實
And she is again well enough to breathe the fall air.
她終于有機會再次呼吸秋天的新鮮空氣了
Our deepest gratitude is often saved
曾經越是理所當然之事
for what we once took for granted.
才越需要我們無盡的感激
Mercy?
梅西
- What is it? - No.
-怎么了  -不
No, my child. No. No.
孩子  不要  不要
The witch!!
巫師
Who's the witch, Mercy?
巫師是誰  梅西
Tell us! Who's the witch?!
告訴我們  誰是巫師
Is he the witch, Mercy?
他是巫師嗎  梅西
Is he?
是他嗎
Mercy?
梅西
Help!
快來幫忙
Will someone help us?!
快來人幫忙
What's happened?
怎么回事
We've lost control.
我們失去控制了
She is no longer ours.
她不再是我們的人了
The hive is restless.
大家躁動不安
Some are beginning to doubt your grand vision for our kind.
有人甚至開始懷疑你的計劃是否利于我們
Who? Give me their names.
是誰  告訴我名字
You're missing the point, child.
這不是重點  孩子
Then perhaps he should make one.
那他也許該告訴我重點
Trials are preceded by accusations.
審判是以指控為前提的
And accusations are predicated upon your control of the girl.
而指控是否成功則取決于你對那女孩的控制
The hunter's moon fast approaches.
狩獵月很快就要到了
Yet the blacksmith
而那個鐵匠
still blithely peddles his wares,
還在盡情兜售自己的鐵器
his blood lost to our cause.
他應該為我們的事業犧牲
How dare you.
豈有此理
Before Mary,
瑪麗未加入之前
we were not feared, but fearful,
不是眾人怕我們  而是我們擔驚受怕
not hunters, but prey.
我們不是獵人  而是獵物
And yet does her strength and vision garner your praise?
可她的力量和計劃得到你的一點贊揚了嗎
No.
沒有
Only your doubt.
只有你的懷疑
The girl has been rendered frail by her circumstance.
那個女孩只是因為身體狀況而日趨虛弱
Nothing more.
僅此而已
My mastery is not of issue.
我對她的控制沒有問題
This is an assurance?
這是你的保證嗎
She needs but a moment of rest.
她只是需要休息一段時間
After which, she will again be strong enough
之后  她就會恢復力量
to point the finger.
去指認他人
Yet another issue remains...
還有個問題沒有解決...
That of John Alden.
約翰·奧登
What of him?
他怎么了
His suspicion of me is palpable.
他明顯在懷疑我
If she cannot abate his threat,
如果她無法解除威脅
then I will be forced to do so myself -- as I see fit.
那我會親自動手  這并無不妥吧
Should you desire John Alden's trust,
如果你想得到約翰·奧登的信任
I would suggest you find a way to earn it.
我建議你想辦法去自己爭取
And, Mary...
至于  瑪麗
Your vision guides us.
你的的目標指引著我們
I will report to the others
我會向其他人報告
that your plan shall resume anon.
你的計劃將繼續進行
We need answers quickly.
我們需要盡快找到答案
And we will get them.
我們會找到的
How?
怎么找
The quickest way one finds answers...
找到答案的最快方法
blame.
就是指責
Is it your intent to rob me
你是想要抹殺我對你
of my remaining faith in you, reverend?
僅存的信心了嗎  牧師
Mrs. Sibley. I didn't hear you arrive.
西布里夫人  我沒注意到您來了
Your charge, simple and clear,
你的職責  簡單明了
is to protect the Lewis girl from further possession.
就是要保護路易絲不再被惡魔附身
And yet...was the episode in the marketplace
然而  在集市里發生的那一幕
not evidence of exactly that?
不正表明這又重演了嗎
We have no proof it was the work of witches.
沒有證據表明這是巫師所為
So you've paid her a visit, then?
這么說你已經去看過她了
You've determined what ails her?
你知道是什么在折磨她了嗎
The pastor says she's resting
牧師說她正在休息
and best not be disturbed.
最好不被打擾
May I ask you a question, reverend?
我能問你個問題嗎  牧師
When your father seeks out demons, does he ask permission?
你的父親搜尋魔鬼之時  他請求許可了嗎
Does he knock on doors
他會禮貌敲門
and offer to come back at a more convenient time?
并答應等到方便的時候再來拜訪嗎
Or does he, armed with the Lord's righteousness,
還是他秉持著上帝的正義
demand the demon answer to him?
命令魔鬼給他回應
My father and I are different men.
父親和我截然不同
We work in different ways.
我們有不同的工作方式
When I summoned a hunter of witches
當我傳召獵人追捕巫師
to protect the people of Salem, it was not you I requested.
從而保護塞勒姆的人民時  我要找的人并不是你
Yet it was you who arrived on our shores.
但來到這里的人卻是你
Do not make me regret settling for my second choice.
別讓我為自己的第二選擇后悔
Captain Alden.
奧登上尉
How fortuitous.
真巧
I was just about to set this on your doorstep.
我正打算把這個放在你的門階上呢
I'll spare you the mystery.
我就不賣關子了
It's a reception tomorrow evening in your honor.
明晚會為你舉辦一個招待會
A reception?
招待會
No. That's not necessary.
不  沒有必要
But it is. You're a selectman now.
已經定了  你現在是行政委員了
And, on a more personal note, a chance to make amends
出于私心  這也是修復我們關系的機會
for my less-than-hospitable behavior since your return.
自打你回來  我表現得似乎不甚友好
Can we trust you'll be in attendance?
你能確定出席嗎
Excuse me, Magistrate.
不好意思  治安官
Lieutenant Hooke.
霍克中尉
John Alden.
約翰·奧登
Now, is this any way to greet the man
你就這么問候
who saved you from those savages?
把你從野蠻人手里救出來的人嗎
What the hell are you doing here?
你來這里做什么
Business, Captain.
做生意  上尉
There is a vessel in port on which I have cargo.
港口有艘船  上面載有我的貨物
And until the quarantine is lifted,
在檢疫結束之前
I am marooned here in your little witch town.
我是被困在這個巫師小鎮了
We had a deal, and it was a simple one...
我們說好的  再簡單不過了
that I was never to set eyes on you again.
我不想再見到你
Yes. Well, you needn't worry.
沒錯  你不必擔心
We're not the same men we were in the war.
我們都不再是打仗時的樣子了
But...
不過
There is something you could do to hasten my departure.
你確實能行個方便讓我早點離開
What is that?
什么事
The girl you spoke of in battle... Mary Wolcott.
戰時你提到的那個女孩  瑪麗·沃科特
Although she's Mary Sibley now, isn't she?
現在她是瑪麗·西布里了  是吧
An introduction with her would certain...
如果將我引薦給她  一定能...
You stay away from Mary.
你離瑪麗遠點
Or what, John?
否則如何  約翰
What will you do?
你會怎么做
What I should have done last time.
做我上次就該做的事
Now, careful, Captain.
小心點  上尉
Before a man makes threats,
一個人撂下狠話之前
he should take stock of what he risks...
應該先掂量所面臨的風險
unless you do not mind me telling the good people of Salem
除非你不介意我告訴塞勒姆的人們
just who John Alden really is...
約翰·奧登到底是個什么樣的人
neither the man nor the war hero he purports to be.
他并非所標榜的錚錚男兒  更不是戰斗英雄
I want you to finish your business with all due haste,
我要你盡快把生意了結了
and then by coach or by steed or by ship, I want you gone.
之后不管你坐車騎馬或者乘船  我要你離開
You have my word.
我向你保證
Mr. Sibley's feeding will have to wait
西布里先生的喂食
until I return from the reception.
得等我從招待會上回來了
Excuse me.
不好意思
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
And you are?
你是哪位
I'm Hooke... William Hooke.
我是霍克  威廉·霍克
Forgive my boldness, but I wondered
原諒我的魯莽   我只是在想
if I might speak to you of your ship detained in port.
或許可以和您談談滯留在港口的船只
As you've doubtless heard, it's under quarantine.
你多半也聽說了  它得接受檢疫
Well, 'tis no bother.
不必麻煩了
I merely mean to board the vessel and retrieve my cargo.
我只想登船取回我的貨物
And risk infection? Or worse?
冒著被感染甚至更嚴重的風險嗎
Well, this must be very valuable cargo, Mr. Hooke.
那想必是很寶貴的貨物了  霍克先生
Sorry.
抱歉
No one's permitted on board.
任何人不得登船
Well, perhaps Mr. Sibley
或許西布里先生
will be more open to reason.
會更明理一些呢
I can assure you, Mr. Hooke,
我能向你保證  霍克先生
my husband and I are of one mind on all matters.
我丈夫與我對所有事務的看法都是一致的
Good evening.
晚安
Mercy, if you can hear me, I beseech you,
梅西  如果你能聽見  我懇求你
speak to me the name
告訴我附身于你
of the vengeful spirit that possesses you.
意欲報復的惡靈到底是誰
Hasn't she suffered enough?
她經歷的苦難還不夠嗎
Which is why I seek to end her suffering...
因此我才要想辦法結束她的苦難
by freeing her from the demon inside.
將她從惡魔手中解救出來
Reverend Mather?
麥哲牧師
Agrimony?
龍牙草
The...apothecary's suggestion.
藥劑師的主意
A herb with no medicinal value.
沒有藥用價值的草藥
- Used historically in exorcisms. - Mmm.
-常用于驅魔術 -沒錯
She wakes.
她醒了
Mercy?
梅西
Can you hear me?
能聽到我說話嗎
Yes, reverend.
是的  牧師
She looks well.
她看起來好多了
Eyes clear.
眼神清澈
Skin temperate to the touch.
體溫也很正常
Bless God.
感謝上帝
My God.
天哪
What is this?
這是怎么一回事
The Barber bled her humors.
理發師給她做了一次放血療法
She hasn't sufficient time to heal.
她的傷口還沒好
Anne.
安
What a lovely surprise.
見到你真是意外之喜
I anticipated only members of the board.
我還以為今晚只有行政委員會出席呢
Oh, I convinced my father to let me attend.
我說服了父親讓我來的
One can't pass up the rare gathering in Salem
如今在塞勒姆沒有絞刑架和憤怒人群的集會
that doesn't involve a noose and an angry mob.
可是越來越少了  我怎么會錯過呢
- Beautiful, isn't it? - Mm.
-很漂亮吧  不是嗎  -當然
A gift from my father.
是我父親送的
May I?
我能看看嗎
Exquisite.
精美至極
If you'll excuse me...
我先失陪一陣
And here I feared the guest of honor
我剛剛還在擔心
wasn't going to make an appearance at his own party.
咱們今晚宴會的主角不會到場呢
Well, I flipped a coin.
我擲了個硬幣
- Heads, I stay home. - And tails?
-正面朝上  我就待家里  -如果是背面呢
I flip again and pray for heads.
我會再扔一次  祈禱這一次是正面
No such luck.
可惜仍不走運
Well, I think you'll find that you have more common ground
我想你會發現  或許你與這些委員會同伴們
with your fellow board members than you would have expected.
有比你想象中更多的共同之處
Oh. They think salem's gone mad, too?
難道他們也認為塞勒姆已經陷入瘋狂了嗎
Enjoy yourself, huh?
請隨意  好嗎
Captain Alden.
奧登上尉
How nice to see you amongst the living --
真高興看到你還活著
so to speak.
打個比方
Valerian root?
纈草根
You've resorted to the coarse tools of the hunters.
你已經不擇手段到使用獵人的那些粗劣工具了嗎
Yes. Well, sadly,
是的  很遺憾
I can no longer take the safety of my loved ones for granted.
如今我無法再置我至親的安全而不顧
Apparently, there are those in Salem
很明顯  塞勒姆里有些人
who are not above threatening the lives of children.
會品行低劣到對孩子下手
She's no child, magistrate.
她可不是孩子  治安官
Certainly not,
至少
judging by the way she lusts for John Alden.
從她對約翰·奧登的愛慕之意便可看出
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
I came straightaway with news.
我一有結果便立刻來通知您了
Mercy Lewis is free of her possessor.
梅西·路易絲已經擺脫了她的控制者
You're certain?
你確定
My exam was thorough.
我的檢查很詳盡
I could glean no remaining evidence of the demon inside.
在她體內我再找不到一絲惡魔殘留的證據
How serendipitous.
那真是萬幸啊
Perhaps beyond good fortune.
或許并不只是好運這么簡單
This is evidence of the witches' waning strength
這表示巫師的力量正在消退
or waxing fear --
他們的恐懼正在加深
A testament to the potency of our resistance.
正說明我們的反抗行動起了作用
Forgive me, uh, Reverend,
恕我無知  牧師
As I am but a layman in these matters,
對于這些事情我知之甚少
but how did she free herself from satan's grasp?
但她又是如何逃出撒旦魔爪的呢
I detected traces of agrimony,
我發現了龍芽草的痕跡
as well as an incision in the girl's abdomen,
還有那女孩腹部的一條傷口
leading to my supposition that an exorcism had been performed.
因此我推測一定是有人對她施行了驅魔術
An exorcism?
驅魔術
A catholic ritual performed in Salem,
在塞勒姆里有人進行著天主教的儀式
and you have the audacity to present this as good news?
你居然還膽敢聲稱這是好消息
Do you know what salem abhors
你知道在塞勒姆
even more than a witch, Reverend?
比巫師更令人憎惡的是什么嗎  牧師
A catholic.
那就是天主教徒
Yet under your most watchful eye,
而如今在你的監視之下
you've now allowed both to flourish.
兩種惡行卻大行其道
When could this have happened, Reverend --
為什么會這樣  牧師
When you were distracted by drink or by whores?
你是被酒精還是妓女給蒙蔽了理智
Mrs. Sibley --
西布里夫人
Replacing demons with heathens is no victory.
用異教徒取代惡魔根本算不上勝利
Seems even when you succeed, reverend,
看起來就算你成功解決了問題  牧師
you find a way to fail.
你仍能找到法子失敗
We live in a time of war,
如今戰爭一觸即發
our enemies hidden among us.
敵人就隱藏在我們身邊
And so there could be no better time than this
此時此刻  我們正需要
to welcome a new ally in our fight
一位新的盟友加入
against the dark forces that threaten our town.
來共同對抗威脅小鎮的黑暗勢力
Witches will be no match for a war hero.
在戰爭英雄面前  巫師不足為懼
The newest member of our board of selectmen --
歡迎我們行政委員會的最新成員
Captain John Alden.
約翰·奧登上尉
What if the witches were not the common folk?
如果巫師并不是普通人呢
Not those who trapped our food nor birthed our babies?
不是以設陷阱為生的獵人  也不是助產的婦女
What if the witches were those we've entrusted to lead?
如果巫師是那些得到我們信任的領導者呢
A member, perhaps, of our most esteemed board?
或許  是我們最尊貴的委員會成員之一
Well, I hope not,
至少  我希望不是
'cause I'm one of you now.
因為如今  我也是你們的一員了
And, together, I trust
我相信  如果我們攜手
we will end the scourge that blights this town.
定能終結侵蝕這個小鎮的禍害
Reverend Mather.
麥哲牧師
I'm sorry, Gloriana --
我很抱歉  格里安娜
Miss Embry --
安布里小姐
But it has been a very trying day,
但今天真是非常忙碌的一天
and I have not yet begun to prepare tomorrow's sermon.
而且我還未開始準備明天的布道
I simply wish to thank you --
我只是想謝謝你
For showing me the depth of your care
昨天在大庭廣眾之下
yesterday in the public house.
讓我看到了你的深切關心
And so you have, Miss Embry.
也謝謝您  安布里小姐
Though I assure you that separating you
但我向您保證
from that unsavory character was a mere act of charity.
我趕走那纏著您的人渣僅僅出于道義
Charity?
道義
So, too, pity.
以及憐憫
Pity and charity?
憐憫和道義
I'm afraid.
恐怕正是
And it had nothing to do with feeling?
與感覺無關嗎
Not beyond the feeling
與我對上帝的
I possess for any of God's needy creatures...
所有苦難子民的感情無異
A hungry child...
就像對饑餓的孩子
A wounded animal.
或是受傷的動物一樣
A whore?
對妓女也一樣
Glori...
格里安...
Miss Embry, you know I detest such words.
安布里小姐  你知道我憎恨那樣的字眼
But in the house of the lord,
但在上帝面前
There can be no deceit.
我們不能有所欺騙
Isn't that what you preach?
這不正是你一直在傳播的嗎
That a whore is a whore?
妓女就是妓女
Just as one would never say "Pity"
但我卻不會用"憐憫"
when they meant "Passion"...
來掩飾"熱情"
"Charity" When they meant "Envy."
用"道義"來粉飾"妒忌"
Envy?
妒忌
At the thought of another man's mouth on mine,
就是當你看到其他男人親吻我
His body pressed against mine...
軀體緊緊地貼著我
His loins enveloped in mine.
下體進入我體內時的那感覺
Lord, forgive her impiety.
上帝啊  請原諒她的不敬
Is that the same lord that you invoke from my bed
這是你在我體內進出時
as you thrust in and out of me?
在我床上呼喚的那位上帝嗎
The same lord that you thank
是我的唇舌在你胸口和股間游走時
as my tongue traces down your chest or up your thigh?
你感謝的那位上帝嗎
That same lord to which I pray
是我向他祈禱
that your promise to return will never be an empty one?
你回來的許諾不再落空的那位上帝嗎
Gloriana, you mustn't be here.
格里安娜  你不能待在這里
Or what?
否則如何
What will you do here... in the house of the lord?
在上帝的處所  你能怎么樣
Cot.. Cot...
柯頓  柯頓
No. Please.
不  別這樣
Mr. Sibley.
西布里先生
My name is Hooke... William Hooke.
我叫霍克  威廉·霍克
And I have cargo on your frigate detained in port.
您泊在港口的船上有我的貨物
Yet your wife refuses to lift the quarantine.
可您夫人卻拒絕解除隔離
Now, whilst Mrs. Sibley's beauty is beyond dispute,
雖然  西布里夫人的美貌驚為天人
What woman truly grasps the necessities of a man's vocation?
但哪能讓女人來掌管男人的事業呢
They...
她們...
S-sir...
先生
Has your illness rendered you deaf and dumb?
您已經病得又聾又啞了嗎
I...
我...
I'm a bit upset with myself, captain.
我對自己有點失望  上尉
Why?
何出此言
I invited you to my home under false pretense.
我邀請你來我家其實別有動機
In hoping to gain your trust,
我想贏得你的信任
I have clearly done the very opposite.
很明顯  這么做卻起了相反的作用
What's your point, magistrate?
您到底想說什么  治安官
Perhaps it would have been wiser for me
也許直接告訴您真相
to simply tell you the truth about who and what I am.
以及我的真實身份  會更明智
And what's that?
那是什么
A concerned father.
一個憂心忡忡的父親
Three days ago, my daughter was spelled...
三天前  我女兒被下了咒
or so I believe.
至少我相信是這樣
And yet when she asked, you...
可她問起時...
I lied... yes.
我說謊了  是的
How could I let her know that there are those out there
我怎么能告訴她
who wish to do her harm?
外面有人想傷害她
You see what they've done to the Lewis girl,
你也看到他們是怎么對路易絲的
Her mind no longer her own.
她已經瘋了
What if my Anne is their next target?
如果我的安就是他們的下一個目標怎么辦
You and I have a common enemy...
你我有著共同的敵人
The witches who would do my Anne and all of us harm.
那些會傷害安和我們所有人的女巫
And who are they?
那她們到底是誰
This remains a mystery.
這仍是個謎團
I must admit, uh...
我必須承認
I underestimated you.
我低估你了
Well, thank you.
謝謝
You are full of far more shit than I thought possible.
你比我想象得還更人渣
Maybe you did not spell Anne.
也許你沒對安下咒
Maybe your explanations have been genuine.
也許你的解釋很誠懇
But I don't think so.
但我不信
I think you're dirty.
我覺得你不是好人
And once I find proof, all of Salem will, too.
一旦我找到證據  整個塞勒姆也會這么想的
He requested you, yet shows no signs of agitation.
他對你提了要求  卻完全沒有躁動的跡象
That will change.
會變的
Breaking into my home?
擅闖民居
Do you know what happens to thieves in Salem?
你知道在塞勒姆  小偷會有什么下場嗎
No.
不知道
But I know what happens to witches.
但我知道女巫會有什么下場
What's this?
這是什么
Perhaps a question best asked of Mr. Sibley.
也許這問題最好由西布里先生來回答
My husband's affliction
我丈夫遭受的病痛
Has robbed him of both reason and sense.
已經剝奪了他的理智和感覺
And yet are either actually required
而這恰是要管理塞勒姆
to point the finger in Salem?
最需要的兩樣東西
I care not for threats, Mr. Hooke.
我可不怕威脅  霍克先生
And I care not to resort to them.
我也沒打算威脅你
So, perhaps, we could avoid bringing this note
也許  我們可以避免
to the attention of the board of selectmen.
將這字條提交給行政委員會
Grant you access to my ship,
所以要么同意你登我的船
or face your most scurrilous accusations?
要么面對你最無恥的指控是嗎
Fine.
好
At midnight, the ship's sentry will be sent home,
半夜時分輪船的守衛會回家
and you can retrieve your cargo.
你可以去拿回你的貨
Now out with you.
現在給我滾
Does my sense betray me?
我的靈感出錯了嗎
He could undo you! All of us!
他能破壞你的計劃  我們的計劃
And so could Mercy.
梅西也可以
The familiar has been cut from her.
靈獸從她身上脫離了
How?
怎么會
An exorcism --
通過驅魔術
performed by her dolt of a father, no doubt.
毫無疑問是她的傻瓜父親干的
So we must replace it.
我們必須用新的代替
And yet why would she accept it a second time?
如今她怎么會再次接受呢
She wouldn't,
她不會
unless there is some part of the girl
除非我們能觸動
to which we can appeal.
那個女孩的某種情感
And what part is that?
哪種情感
The same part you once touched in me --
就是你曾經觸動過我的那個部分
the deep, small piece of her that longs for a better life.
她內心深處對更好的生活的小小憧憬
You must move quickly, then.
那你得快點行動
I, alone, will take charge of Mr. Hooke.
我會一個人對付霍克先生
But, Tituba...
但是緹圖芭
These are perilous times.
如今事態嚴峻
No blood must lead back to our door.
千萬不能讓任何人抓著我們的把柄
Do you understand?
明白嗎
Perfectly.
完全了解
Had I known you were a friend of John Alden's,
要是我早知道你是約翰·奧登的朋友
I would have found another courier.
我會另找其他送貨員
I can assure you, we are not friends.
我向你擔保我們不是朋友
If you knew the truth of the man,
你要是知道那人的真面目
You would rethink such an accusation.
你這么譴責我之前就會三思了
And what truth is that?
什么真面目
In any case,
無論如何
the impediment has been removed.
阻礙已除
The package shall be yours by midnight.
半夜包裹就是你的了
You did not speak my name to her?
你沒有向她透露我的名字吧
I did as instructed.
我遵囑行事
But, still, I can't help but wonder -- this parcel --
不過我還是禁不住在想  那個包裹
You have been paid well not to wonder,
你已得到豐厚報酬  其他不必多想
Mr. Hooke.
霍克先生
Mercy.
梅西
Leave me.
離我遠點
I won't leave you.
我不會離開的
I can't.
我不能
You need me.
你需要我
You're a liar.
騙子
I don't need you.
我不需要你
When you resist me,
我附身于你的時候
When you point at a demon that only you can see,
你指出一個僅你可見的魔鬼的時候
What do they do?
他們做了什么
They shave your locks.
他們剪去你的頭發
They weep for your wretched soul.
為你可憐的靈魂哭泣
Go away! Go!
走開  快走開
Without me, you are but a girl,
沒有我  你只是個
weak and ordinary.
軟弱又平凡的女孩
But with me inside you, you are...
但是讓我附身于你
omnipotent.
你就會無所不能
Hush, now.
別哭了
Give them no cause to pity you.
別給他們理由可憐你
Give them only reason to fear you.
讓他們只能敬畏你
No! No!
不  不要
Open, girl.
張嘴  孩子
Open your mouth.
張嘴吧
Yes.
這就對了
Just like that.
就像那樣
He has chosen you to be his vessel on earth.
它選擇了你成為它地球上的使者
There is no greater honor
能為它服務
than to be in his service.
是至高榮耀
What? What?
怎么了  怎么了
What? What? What?
怎么回事  怎么回事
She is mine.
她是我的
Tituba?
緹圖芭
Mary is in trouble.
瑪麗出事了
I am but a servant, captain,
我只是個仆人  上尉
unentitled to such an intrusion.
沒有權利如此冒犯
What is it?
到底是什么事
I fear you and my mistress
恐怕您和我的女主人
share a common adversary --
有一個共同的敵人
Mr. Hooke.
霍克先生
How did you know that he --
你怎么知道他
I saw you quarreling in the warren off the square.
我看見您在鎮中心外的大雜院里和他爭執
He demands access to my mistress' ship.
他要求進入我女主人的船
Why?
為什么
To retrieve some worthless parcel, as he claims?
是像他說的那樣只為找個沒有價值的包裹
Or does he harbor darker intent?
還是他包藏禍心
He plans to rob her.
他計劃打劫她
So my mistress fears.
我的女主人也如此擔心
Why did Mrs. Sibley allow him to board that vessel?
西布里夫人為什么準許他登船呢
He left her no choice.
她別無選擇
He threatened to spread false rumor of an affair --
他以散播關于我女主人
with you, captain.
和你有染的虛假消息來要挾  上尉
She sought to reason with him, but --
她本想與他理論  但是
He is not a man that responds to reason.
他并不是個講理的人
Mrs. Sibley would lash me if she knew I had come,
西布里夫人要是知道我找你一定會責罵我
but I fear Mr. Hooke will be her ruin.
但是我擔心霍克先生會毀了她
Unless --
除非
Speak, girl.
說吧  姑娘
Unless there be a man who desires to stop him.
除非有人能阻止他
You have feelings for him, don't you?
你喜歡他  是嗎
"Him"?
他是誰
Must I say his name?
一定要我說出他的名字嗎
Was it not obvious to all who were present this evening?
這對今晚所有在場的人來說不是顯而易見嗎
Is it not a woman's prerogative
這不是一個女人應有的特權嗎
to choose which man she fancies?
選擇自己喜歡的男人
It is.
是沒錯
Just as it is a father's prerogative
就像這也是父親的特權
to protect his daughter's heart
去保護他女兒的心
from those he feels will do it harm.
不被那些可能會傷害她的人接近
John Alden, for instance.
譬如約翰·奧登
Why do you say this?
你為什么要這么說
Because he doesn't curry your favor,
就因為他不像塞勒姆那些毛躁的
like every other twitchy young man in Salem?
年輕人一樣對你阿諛奉承嗎
No. That is not it.
不  這不是原因
How could he ever be yours truly
他永遠都是屬于瑪麗·西布里
when he always was and always will be Mary Sibley's?
又怎能成為你的摯愛
Their history is no secret.
他們的歷史不是個秘密
But it is just that -- history.
但也僅此而已  是個歷史
She is a married woman now.
她是個已婚的女人了
And do you suppose Mary Sibley will idly stand by
你真的以為瑪麗·西布里會站在一旁
while you claim that which she rightfully considers
看著你占據她認為屬于自己
to be her own?
的東西嗎
You fear her, father.
你怕她  父親
I do not.
我不怕
You are but a child. You don't understand.
你只是個孩子  你不明白
A child?
一個孩子
A moment ago, you agreed I was a woman.
不久前  你還同意我是個女人
It's not for debate.
這沒什么可爭論的
- By whose command? - By mine!
-到底誰說了算  -我說了算
Your father!
你的父親
Your lord and master!
你的所有者和主人
I forbid you to have further contact with captain Alden!
我禁止你與奧登上尉今后再有任何來往
Or what?
不然呢
What punishment awaits me?
我會受到怎樣的懲罰
Will you crush the life from me, as you do your enemies?
你會奪走我的生命嗎  就像你對敵人一般
Or just my spirit,
或者僅僅是我的靈魂
as you do those you love?
像你對所愛之人做的一樣
Quiet!
閉嘴
Not one word more!
不準再說了
Put it down.
把那放下
No.
不
This parcel belongs to me.
這個箱子屬于我
A claim that even Mary Sibley cannot dispute.
這權利連瑪麗·西布里也無法奪走
I'm not here on her behalf.
我不是代表她來的
Now put it down.
現在  把它放下
Ask yourself, captain...
問問你自己  上尉
Is it really worth it?
這真的值得嗎
What?
什么
The cost of settling old scores.
解決老恩怨的代價
What would be the charge
如果被治安官發現你所做的事情
if the magistrate knew what you did?
你覺得會被判什么罪
Murder?
謀殺
Treason?
叛國
Both?
二者皆有
You know what happened that day.
你知道那天發生了什么
Yes.
是的
I watched you spill innocent blood.
我看著你潑灑無辜的鮮血
Without regret or remorse.
沒有一絲后悔與憐憫
Men slaughtered like animals.
多少人像畜牲一般被屠殺
All of them -- dead.
所有人  都死了
Not all of them.
不是所有人
We had a deal, Mr. Hooke --
我們有過交易  霍克先生
The day you fell to your knees and begged for your life
那天你跪在地上求饒
that should I let you live,
說如果我放你一條生路
we would never cross paths again.
你將不會再出現在我面前
You didn't hold up your end.
你沒有遵守約定
Now, think this through, captain.
好好想清楚  上尉
Oh, I have --
我當然有
thoroughly.
很詳細地想過
And the only life I lament that day was the one I spared.
那天我唯一后悔的就是沒有趕盡殺絕
A man should keep his promises, Mr. Hooke.
你該遵守約定的  霍克先生
So you're...just going to slit my throat here,
所以  你打算在這里割了我的喉
like some yellow horse?
像那些印第安野蠻人一樣
No.
不
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Sleeplessness seems to be epidemic this evening.
看來今晚大家似乎都為失眠而困擾
Do you remember
你還記得
the last time we spoke,
我們上一次
in the shadow of the graveyard?
在墓地陰影中的談話嗎
Of course.
當然記得
The promises we made?
我們做出的約定
You would return within a year.
你會在一年內回來
And you would breathlessly wait.
而你將屏息等待
Were they lies?
那些都是謊言嗎
No.
不是
They were wishes.
這些是愿望
Made by those that knew nothing of the world.
不諳世事的人許下的愿望
And now?
現在呢
We know.
我們明白了
What we desire and what we must do to survive
我們的心之所向往往卻與生存所需
are often at odds.
背道而馳
It's, uh, late, captain.
很晚了  上尉
It is.
是很晚了
Long past my bedtime.
我就寢時間早過了
I wish you sweet dreams, Mary.
祝你好夢  瑪麗
Perhaps they've already begun.
或許這已經是一場美夢了
I know what you are.
我知道你是什么東西